By LESAIGNEUR
Sync October 2022
And of course I set it
to Icelandic time because,
we share a love
of the aurora borealis Gordy.
And...
you have no idea how to tell time.
Great gift Dad.
Way to think things through.
Somehow, you would think that a man
who can send a rocket into space,
would be able to manage
a halfway decent birthday present.
Nope.
You know Gordy, all things considered,
maybe my gift isn't so bad after all.
Hey Gordy!
Surprise!
Now there is a gift.
Here you go Gordy.
Happy birthday.
Oh, beautiful Haley.
Gordy!
Good morning on what is
sure to be a windy one.
We have a high wind warning
for the L.A. County coast and valleys
with some clouds sure to come in
around 10:00 a.m.
And even though the high gust
warning will...
expire mid to late morning,
you will still want to keep...
The search for a group of missing hikers
is set to resume this morning,
just outside Agua Dulce.
The tour group went out two days ago
and on the Pacific Crest Trail
but didn't come back
as expected that night.
Crews started searching
yesterday morning...
And traffic is already backed up,
due to an accident
on the southbound 101.
It is 7:44 with Bo and Ives.
Bang.
Come on.
Down, down.
Down, down, down.
Bang!
Yes a good boy.
Up. Up, up.
Ok, up!
Up, up.
Got to keep our heads up
out the clouds on this one.
I know.
Now we land this...
Yeah.
Like Six Guns.
I mean, we really put on a show,
well...
you know they are gonna
bring us back for the sequel.
Well,
we sure as hell ain't
got to sell no more horses.
So just execute.
And we ain't got no more problems.
You good?
Where your sister?
What's that about?
She is supposed to be here.
Yeah.
Goddamn it.
Thought I told you to fix the damn walker.
You hear that?
Pops.
Come on, come on. Pop.
Firefly.
What else? What else?
Ghost.
Beethoven.
Commodore.
Yeah.
Virgil.
You good. You good.
You good, man. You good.
Ghost.
You good. You good. You good.
Pops?
Lucky.
Pops.
Commodore.
Pops!
OJ.
Hi horsie.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't look him in the eyes, please.
Ok.
You ready to do the safety meeting?
I am gonna need like five...
my team is almost here.
Your team is not here?
Ok.
Hold.
Sorry, I got the horse guy
talking to me too. What's up?
Copy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Ms. Bonnie Clayton on set.
Here she is everybody.
Take a look at all...
of that.
Fynn, this is OJ our horse trainer.
You remember these guys from Flash Point.
Yeah. Hi.
Your name is OJ?
Yeah, Otis Junior.
Where is the o-the other guy?
The-the the senior guy?
Dude he died.
About six months ago.
A bunch of random shit fell out of a plane.
So I guess we are stuck
with Junior over here.
No.
Yeah.
Ok.
Fuck.
Great.
Ant, how we looking?
Yeah good,
if we are selling a horse's ass.
That's...
legendary cinematographer
Antlers Holst over here...
Let's go ahead and spin the horse.
But you had said hold so...
And now I am saying spin.
Let's go.
Great. And while that's spinning,
can we get makeup?
Makeup for Ms. Bonnie Clayton.
Please.
Hold on.
Can you step away from the back please?
They told me to come here.
Good call OJ...
Tell you what,
let's do a quick safety meeting.
Guys,
this is OJ, our horse trainer.
Take it away.
Kill the music please.
My name is OJ.
I think my sister is gonna be
here in a minute.
Little louder please.
We cannot hear you in the back.
I said we are animal wranglers
with Haywood Hollywood Horses.
And...
did you know the...
very first assem...
Hey yo!
Excuse me. Sorry.
I am so sorry about that.
Let me do that.
Sorry, brother.
Safety meeting.
Yeah.
Hello! How you all doing?
Sorry for the tardiness.
My name is Emerald, that's OJ,
and we are your animal wranglers today
with Haywood Hollywood Horses.
Now,
did you know that the very first assembly
of photographs in sequential order
to create a motion picture was a...
two second clip
of a Black man on a horse?
Yes it was.
Look it up.
Now, I know you guys know,
Eadweard Muybridge,
the grandfather of motion pictures
who took the pictures that created that clip,
but does anybody know the name of
the Black jockey that rode the horse?
No.
Nope?
I mean, the very first stuntman,
animal wrangler and movie star
all rolled into one,
and there is literally no record of him.
That man was a Bahamian jockey
that went by the name
of Alistair E. Haywood.
And he is my great great grandfather.
Great.
There is another great,
grandfather.
That's why back at the Haywood Ranch,
as the only Black owned
horse trainers in Hollywood,
we like to say,
since the moment pictures could move,
we had skin in the game.
Alright let's get into some...
safety precautions while
we are on set, shall we?
Number one,
please refrain from making any loud noises,
sudden movements
and keep your cell phones off.
We would really appreciate that.
Two, if you see anything
that looks or feels unsafe,
contact me,
OJ or your second in chain of command.
And three,
let's have a great shoot!
And I am Emerald Haywood.
I direct, write, produce, act.
I do a little...
♪ Singing on the side ♪
Motorcycles, baby look.
I-I make a mean grilled cheese
if you are looking for crafty, just...
just holler at me.
Ok, that was great.
That was, that was a lot.
Let's do a rehearsal.
Yeah?
Rehearsal?
Rehearsing we should.
We should do one. Rehearsing.
I think, I think he might need a break.
Yeah, we will rehearse one first,
and then break yeah?
Well, I am ready to do one.
OJ, she is...
she is ready to do one.
Tell the horse we are ready to do one.
VFX, can we get the ball
in here while we have a sec?
Em?
VFX.
OJ can... you can step off.
Step out please. Step off.
Yeah, yeah.
Step out.
Em?
What's the horse's name?
Lucky.
Lucky?
Is he?
VFX!
Yeah. Em?
OJ, let's step off.
You calling me?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I am trying to work.
What did I tell you about that man?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Medic.
Are you ok?
Look, maybe it's just too soon?
Yeah, it's not the gig.
Not ready yet.
Right?
We need it man.
No I know.
Your dad left an enormous hole.
I know that.
But don't worry, there will be others.
Alright? I am sorry.
And...
Sorry.
Just, you tell her sorry.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Come on now.
Oh, where is VFX?
Alright.
You got it.
Sorry that was...
So where am I dropping you?
I am go up with you.
I need to get some shit.
My little girl said you know,
I could crash at her place so...
I will be gone in the morning.
So I am gonna drive you back tomorrow?
I can find a ride.
But I mean like...
can I get fun OJ out this bitch?
Because this wackass OJ
is really, making me feel
like I am not loved.
Is that how you want
your little sister to feel?
What happened to Gold Rush?
Gold Rush went bankrupt.
It's been this for three years.
Cowboys and cowgirls,
just a little heads up.
Join us Fridays,
at 5:30 p.m. for the brand,
spanking new Jupiter's Claim
Star Lasso Experience.
Oh, shi...
Come on.
I am sorry, you all. I am sorry.
Photo bomb.
You ruined it.
Yeah, my bad.
Gold I tell you.
They got gold up in here.
Lucky.
Hang tight.
I will be back.
How many you sold?
How many?
Ten.
You sold ten of Pops' horses?
I am gonna get them back.
Can you stay out here?
Why?
I am developing a business relationship
and you are a liability right now.
How am I a liability?
How are you a lia...
Don't promote your fucking
side shit on the job.
Oh, my God.
Actor, singer, dancer,
seamstress, motorcycles.
You want to promote something,
promote this business.
No OJ. No.
First of all, that's not my side shit.
This is.
And second of all, if anybody has a liability...
Fuck you.
No, fuck you.
Hi there. It's Amber again
from Jupe's Claim.
It does look like we were able
to squeeze out a couple of...
extra press passes for the...
upcoming friends and family preview.
No apology necessary.
This is in reference to the biggest,
bestest,
brand new live show we have
coming up here at the park,
Come in.
OJ.
Thanks for coming up.
How you doing?
This is my sister Em.
Hi there.
So...
who did you bring me?
Lucky.
He is my second best horse, you know...
He lost focus.
So...
I meanl did too but I can't fire myself.
That's good.
Oh, hey, hold up.
This you?
You literally the Asian kid from Kid Sheriff?
Em, Em, Em, Em...
No it's ok.
Yeah I was...
I was Lil' Jupe.
Dude, you were literally my favorite.
You mind if I get a picture real quick?
Hey, you mind if we talk?
Yes. Of course.
Please,
browse away.
Su casa es mi casa.
Thank you. I sure will.
So...
same deal yeah? Eleven five?
Yeah. Thank you.
That's 3D. Yeah.
Whatever happened to that Black boy?
He was good.
Stop, stop.
I actually wanted to...
lay some groundwork,
to a pathway of-of...
buying some of them back.
Alright?
Yeah.
Yeah. Totally.
Yeah?
Actually...
OJ the offer I made your dad
is still on the table.
Let me... Let...
Yo, wait a minute.
So...
that...
OJ, have I shown you this?
This is in reference
to the Gordy's Home incident.
Gordy's Home.
Yeah, yeah.
So Gordy's Home,
is a short lived but fabled sitcom
I starred in in '96 after Kid Sheriff blew up.
Yeah my pops told me about this show.
The...
the monkey went crazy or some shit.
You know,
I usually charge a fee for this.
Oh, damn.
Tada.
That's the first exploding fist bump.
What? Really?
You all came up with that?
So, as I was saying,
Gordy's Home began airing
in the fall of '96...
and it was an immediate hit.
Ratings were huge.
Pretty good reviews.
Just really took off.
Yeah.
Then...
one day...
we were shooting an episode
in season two entitled,
Gordy's Birthday.
And...
boom.
One of the chimps that plays Gordy just...
just hit his limit.
And it was six minutes
and 13 seconds of havoc.
Network tried to bury hit but...
it was a spectacle.
People are just obsessed.
You are kidding me.
OJ, you said you heard about that?
Maybe that's why they don't let you use chimps.
That's part of the reason.
There is a growing Gordy's Home
fan base out there now.
This Dutch couple paid me 50K
to come in here and spend the night.
I didn't ask.
That's crazy.
So what happened really man?
You have not seen
the Bad Gordy sketch on SNL?
I mean, they pretty much
nailed it better than I could.
No?
Saturday Night Live?
Darrell Hammond as Tom.
Ana Gasteyer as Phyllis.
Cheri Oteri as Mary Jo Elliot.
Scott Wolf is the host.
He is me.
But of course, the star of the sketch...
is Chris,
goddamn Kattan as Gordy,
and he is...
undeniable, ok?
Bit goes like this.
Everyone is trying to celebrate
Gordy's birthday,
but every time,
Gordy hears
something about the jungle,
Gordy Kattan...
goes off.
And it's...
it's Kattan.
He is just crushing it.
He is a force of nature.
He is...
killing on that stage.
Yeah.
It's legendary.
Legendary shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, I am gonna have to go ahead
look that one up on YouTube.
Details you know?
Totally.
I got some work I got to do.
So we ain't gonna chill tonight, nothing?
You want to work?
Hell no.
So, what was the offer?
Jupe?
Yeah.
He offered to buy the ranch.
Oh, really?
That's interesting. How much?
Why?
Because...
I am trying to see how big
of a dumb-ass you are.
Big dumb-ass probably.
So I guess you don't want to see
what's good with Dad liquor cabinet then?
I got that hobby weed too actually.
That's all you had to say then.
Say the hobby weed.
That's all you had to say,
just let me know.
You should have dropped that at the top.
I got the hobby weed, you know.
Ok, your reflexes are still quick like...
I ain't mad at it.
I am watching.
Drink.
Oh shit.
Remember Jean Jacket?
Yeah good horse.
Supposed to be my first horse actually.
I was just talking to my therapist
about this not too long ago.
Therapist?
Yes.
I fuck one on occasion sometimes.
I was telling her that,
for my ninth birthday I was supposed
to get to train Jean Jacket.
But then Pops got some Western and...
Jean Jacket was not mine no more.
Classic Otis Senior.
I distinctly remember...
standing right here at this window,
watching you all train my horse.
My horse.
Pops never looked up at me.
OJ, come on.
You did it nigga.
Remember?
It was Scorpion King actually.
It was not a Western.
That was the first job Pops took me on.
Was not much fun.
Ended up using camels anyways so...
The point is...
Yeah fuck the point.
Yo, that man was hardheaded as fuck.
And so are you.
That's it.
But at the end of the day you got to...
you got to admit man, Pops...
Pops did something
when he made this place.
He changed the industry.
That's real.
I can't just let that go.
Why is Ghost in the arena?
What's good?
Yeah.
♫ ♫ ♫
Hey yo, Em.
Em!
♫ ♫ ♫
Turn it down!
♪ Your generation believed in talk ♪
♪ Alright! ♪
♪ Scared of the very steps in which ♪
Hey!
Where he going?
What if I...
What if I told you...
you will leave here different?
See,
every Friday,
for the last six months...
my family and...
I bore witness
to an absolute
spectacle.
You see it? The power?
Where is Ghost?
I don't know.
Hold on.
Boom.
Power went out.
See?
Rewind.
Stop.
Ghost talking about, I ain't listening.
I am not trained.
I do whatever the fuck I want.
What?
What did you see?
What's a bad miracle?
They got a word for that?
Nope.
They said it was a prop plane
or something that killed Pops.
That shit ain't never made sense to me.
Then tonight,
I heard Ghost make a sound,
I ain't never heard a horse make.
What did you see?
It was big.
How big?
Big.
What did it look like?
I don't know.
It was fast.
Too fast.
Too quiet to be a plane.
OJ.
Are you saying what I think you are saying?
I am telling you man,
we don't need a lot.
We just need enough to make our shit
look different from what's out there.
You get what I am saying like...
You know I ain't trying
to run it up.
I just was looking online,
and I seen a lot of shit.
You know I am broke right?
We will use my money.
Ok, shut up. Look.
Alright.
There it is.
Five to a hundred K.
Well read it.
You read it, dyslexic ass.
The point is a website like,
Cyber Dominion
will pay five to a hundred K for...
photographic evidence of UFOs and shit.
A hundred K?
And that's just what I saw on the first go.
Now that I am thinking about it,
fuck Cyber Dominion.
This shit right here is a moment,
our moment.
We set it up,
release it the right way,
man, I am talking rich and famous for life.
How you doing? You look pretty.
She look like she got a big house.
How?
How what? How we put it out?
Well, that's what I am saying.
We don't just go for
the quick cash in, ok?
We-we go to the most credible platform,
to do the story.
What's that like Oprah?
Yeah.
Like Oprah for example.
After that, everybody want in.
Well, I am saying there is plenty
of videos of flying shit online.
I saw one the other day.
That was not on Oprah.
Nigga, I didn't say Oprah.
You said Oprah.
You love Oprah.
Look, all I am saying is
all that shit online is fake.
Low quality.
Ain't nobody gonna get what we gonna get.
What we gonna get?
The shot.
What shot?
The money shot.
Undeniable, singular the...
the Oprahshot.
The Oprahshot?
Excuse me.
Hi. I can help you over here.
Hi.
Thank you for shopping at Fry's.
Did you guys find everything
you are looking for today?
Yes... Angel.
Great.
Actually, do you have a card with us?
No, thank you.
Would you like one because it...
No thank you.
Would you like one of
our tech support personnel
to help you with the installation?
No, no, no, no, no, thank you.
Appreciate you.
Alright, no help with the install.
Suit yourself.
Is it a hard install?
Well for me no.
You are not gonna be able to do it.
What happened?
Did you guys get robbed?
Yeah, you know.
A lot of blackouts.
Take the camera out from time to time.
All these new cameras,
they have backup battery power so...
you should be fine.
But the outages affect the power
in the battery shit too,
like cell phones.
Ok. Alright.
Cell phones,
they don't just drop in power.
Right?
I mean, maybe your WiFi drops out
whenever your system dips.
So,
that's technology.
Ok, or maybe you are in a UFO hot spot.
No one believes in that.
What's up?
Damn.
Did not realize
you guys were this far out.
I don't mind though.
Smell of...
horse shit and fresh air.
Right?
Look at me man.
Fuck.
Don't do that. Don't yell.
Sorry man.
Sorry if I was like
a little shut down this morning.
Just got out of a four year relationship.
You were fine.
I know it's gonna sound fucking cliché alright,
but I thought that she was the one,
you know?
Is this gonna take longer than an hour?
Oh, shit, yeah.
I' am go ahead and pop out.
Where you going?
I got to go to the store
and get something.
Don't worry about it.
You need anything?
Yo.
Her name was...
Rebecca Diaz.
Yep, keep an eye out for her.
She is an actress, model,
you know?
She booked a pilot on The CW, so...
Yeah fucking left me.
Yeah, fucking CW.
So, thing about this camera...
Actually, can it swivel up?
Yeah.
Boom.
Little more.
More. Ok.
Up.
Yeah.
Do you know they don't call them
UFOs anymore?
It's fucking UAP is now.
Why they got to change the name?
Yeah.
Exactly.
No, fuck it.
I-I will tell you why they...
changed the name...
alright, it's because they...
want to keep us in the dark.
Remember when they declassified
all that UFO footage a couple years ago?
Yeah. Well people started paying attention.
So they changed the name to UAPs.
And no one knows
what the fuck a UAP is,
so everyone lost interest.
I saw that-that Navy clip.
Could not really see them, though.
Could have been better.
It's shitty footage...
of exact proof,
that there is an alien civilization
out there in the universe.
So, who is that?
Come on man.
The little guys with the big eyes.
Yeah. There is lots of theories.
Either they are...
intergalactic travelers looking for peace
or...
futuristic humans,
coming back in time to stop us
from destroying the planet,
or...
they are fucking world killers.
Planetary destroyers.
And that means that they have
been fucking watching us
and studying us, waiting for
the perfect time,
to beam us up
and shove metal probes up
our fucking asses.
Cool.
An-anyway, Ancient Aliens,
History Channel.
Watch that shit.
Hey!
Come on! Help a nigga out!
Hey.
Know where I could find me
a couple of big strong fellas?
You good?
I am good.
What?
What's that?
Oh this?
You know just...
training horses
we ordered that I picked up.
Where did you get it from?
Don't worry about it.
Now come on, help me out.
Got you.
Ok so... so what is that?
Is it like bait?
I told you.
It is a decoy for horse training.
Ok.
Shit.
See?
OJ.
We good.
I mean, he don't know shit.
Oh, no.
You guys are doing something shady.
Hey there!
Hey!
You can stay right there though!
Sure!
What's up?
We are setting up a decoy!
For horse training!
Oh good!
You know, we got some of those!
Where did you get...
Where did you get yours?
Yeah...
I am not really sure!
My wife would know!
Ok!
Thanks for stopping by!
Why the...
You don't live here.
Sorry.
Trying to help.
Sure thing!
Hey.
I wanted to invite you to our...
new family live show!
Friday!
At 5:00 p.m.!
Ok!
Thumbs u... thumbs up.
Should I do it?
Yeah, do it.
Thumbs up!
And so,
the router is in the shed.
I set it up so if the power goes down
on camera A,
camera B is pointed at the sky to catch...
whatever might have taken it out.
And vice versa.
So...
Thank you.
I mean, you are really not gonna tell me
what the fuck is going on?
You will know soon enough.
Cool, cryptic.
Fucking dicks.
I can monitor the feeds remotely myself,
if you want.
Free of charge.
Hell no.
No.
Wham, bam, thank you ma'am.
One more thing.
You will be getting a call,
from my supervisor asking,
how my service was.
Five stars Angel.
Five stars.
Thank you.
So what now?
I don't know.
What you want to do?
I am-Whatever you want to do.
Well, I got some work I got to do.
I am gonna go out...
That's a good one.
I am talking today to women who say
they have been abducted
by aliens from another planet.
May I briefly say, I don't know for a fact
that they are from another planet.
Well, you know you were not
in Kansas anymore...
And I was not wearing red shoes
that I could click together either.
Yeah, yeah.
♪ Living in a bamboo hut ♪
♪ In a little old seaport town ♪
♪ Three kids on the floor ♪
Nope.
Nope, I am out.
I am going. Fuck this shit.
Ok.
Oh shit!
Fuck off.
Give us back our property.
Don't mess with Jupiter's Claim!
Come on.
What happened?
The Park kids.
Jupe's sons.
And they let Clover out man.
What?
They trying to prank Haywood?
It's on!
Hey. You stole their horse.
Yeah.
Hey.
Shit.
What's up Nessie?
Not much. Just stocking shit.
You know, pretty much regular.
Oh, shit!
I need to take my ass to bed.
Who this?
Yo, it's Angel from Fry's.
Just calling to tell you that
there is a bug on camera A.
I know.
Wait, I thought I told you
not to watch our shit.
I know, I know.
Camera B is down.
What?
Like Ancient fucking Aliens down.
Hey!
Hey. Hi.
Eme-Emerald,
can you please, get the bug off the thing?
Get the bug off the fucking thing!
Shit.
What do you see? Do you...
do you see like lights...
or anything like a-a fucking saucer?
It's in the cloud.
OJ!
It's in the cloud!
Yeah, nah, nah, nah.
Run, OJ! Run!
Shit.
Hello?
Are you ok?
It's fine.
Come on.
Ok.
It's still on.
The camera.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Ok, you fucking praying mantis.
Alright bitch.
You like Sour Patch Kids?
Alight man.
Where your shit? Let's go.
Have not seen one of those in a minute.
Fucking praying mantis.
That motherfucker better pray
I don't ever see him,
because if I do, I am eat him.
Let's go.
Where?
Man I don't know.
I got me a little situation in Atwater
texting me back right now.
It's not coming again tonight.
I don't care.
No.
No. Shit.
Bro.
I ain't never seen,
no shit like this.
It ain't worth it.
No. nope.
It's too much.
You should go then.
I got to get up early anyway.
I got mouths to feed.
Shit.
Shit, shit, shit!
You hear that?
Ghost out there.
Acting all...
territorial.
I guess some animals ain't fit to be trained.
Hello?
Hi.
Is this Antlers Holst?
Who is this?
Hey yeah. I am Emerald Haywood.
We met a couple days ago
at the commercial.
Oh yeah, horse girl. Sure.
I remember you and your brother.
Yeah horse boy.
He is here too.
The descendants of the jockey.
Yeah.
Guess I am talking
to motion picture royalty then.
How did you get the number?
I got it from the call sheet.
So we have a project, and...
you know, what if I told you
it was the offer of a lifetime?
Yeah, hopefully not my lifetime.
That's a good one.
I am be real with you.
We don't have a lot of money
to pay you up front.
You know, not like you are used to...
but...
Yeah.
I tend to do one for them
so I can do one for me so...
what is it?
Reality.
Oh no.
Documentary.
Doc-Documentary.
Oh that's better.
So again, what's it about?
It's about the shit dreams is made of baby.
Listen, horse girl.
I got a...
pretty damn superb...
lemon tart in the oven
I am about to serve to
ten of my closest friends so...
Stop. Stop.
Oh, hold on one second.
What?
He is not here for that.
Look, look, no.
Don't be cute.
Stick to the plan.
I don't go to your job,
Say it!
And knock a horse's dick
out your damn hand.
Hello?
Yeah.
Yeah my bad. We good man.
According to...
American Cinema magazine,
you make the cinematically
impossible...
possible.
Well,
we looking for the impossible shot.
That's impossible.
Antlers.
There is something out here in Agua Dulce,
and you are probably
the only person in the world
that can get it on film.
That's it.
Horse girl,
this dream you are chasing,
the one where you end up
at the top of the mountain,
all eyes on you...
it's the dream you never wake up from.
I don't like him.
Holy shit. It's real.
I don't know what you are doing here but...
it was illegal for you to...
spy on us like that.
Wait you...
you don't know?
Ok, tell me when you see it.
There.
Doesn't move.
Exactly.
What?
Look at that.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, ok.
I went back and scrubbed
through the footage,
and that cloud has been right there
at least since I set the cameras up.
Yeah, now you mention it,
I have probably been looking
at the same damn cloud
every day for the last six months.
Shit.
So I mean,
that's them in there.
And we have been recording it,
so we got it.
Right?
Yeah.
Why you saying yeah like that?
We have proof of aliens on video. I...
Yeah, I would not call it proof.
Are you serious?
Look, I have seen crazy weather
phenomenons online before.
That's all I am saying.
He is right.
It's good, but it ain't it.
Ain't Oprah.
Ok.
Are you guys telling me...
that there is an alien spaceship...
in that fucking cloud right there?
It doesn't move like a ship.
What you mean OJ?
What if it's not a ship?
Alright Gordy, we are almost ready buddy.
Here we go buddy.
Come on.
He is ready.
Set.
Here we go.
And... action.
And of course, I set it to Icelandic time
because we share a love
of the aurora borealis Gordy.
And,
you have no idea how to tell time.
Great gift Dad.
Way to think things through.
Somehow, you would think that a man
who can send a rocket into space
would be able to manage
a halfway decent birthday present.
Nope.
You know, Gordy...
all things considered,
maybe my gift isn't so bad after all.
Hey Gordy.
Surprise!
Now that is a gift.
Sorry. My...
That's alright.
Pick it up from there.
Wait a minute.
What happened to we both failed
at finding good...
presents?
Here you go Gordy.
Happy birthday.
Beautiful Hayley.
Hey, hey, hey. No.
No, no! Down! Down! Gordy!
Down!
No. Stop!
Stop that!
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, Gordy, no! No!
D-D-Down! Down! Down!
You sit down!
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
No Gordy!
Stop!
No! No!
Seven just on scene.
Oh, my God.
Feeling good?
Yeah.
Feeling good.
Good.
There we go.
Run it.
Run it one more time babe.
Ok.
What if I told you...
Yo.
It's... storm is coming.
Just tarping up,
just to be safe.
Hey, where you going?
I am get Lucky.
Now, we are not gonna let
a few clouds kill our fun today,
are we folks?
So without further ado,
welcome to the Jupiter's Claim,
Star Lasso Experience!
How is everyone feeling today?
Alright.
It's quite a doozy today.
I want to thank you guys
for coming out here.
But first,
how about another round of applause
for my Amber?
I will tell you, that woman is a saint
for putting up with all my craziness.
And to the knuckleheads up there.
The staff. Shoutout.
Alright.
Alright, that's enough.
I also want to give a special thanks to...
an old costar of mine,
and my first crush,
Mary Jo Elliott everyone!
Yeah.
Alright.
You ready?
Oh, come on.
That ain't nothing.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
You are chosen.
What if I told you...
that in about an hour...
you will leave here...
different?
See,
every Friday...
for the last six months,
my family and I...
have bore witness
to an absolute...
spectacle.
One that you will be seeing here,
today.
So let me take you back to that first night.
Right here in this exact spot,
I had come over to wrangle
a chestnut horse,
named Trigger.
Now,
I could barely see my hand
in front of my face for the fog...
but I swear...
on my wife...
and children's lives
that at 6:13 p.m.,
I see...
a flying saucer,
descend through the mist.
Old Trigger took off straight into the gulch.
And well...
it's like he was going home.
Now, just to be clear...
what we saw...
was a flying saucer.
No doubt about that.
Slightly flatter in the front,
with a circular hole in the bottom
about two school bus lengths wide.
Ladies and gentlemen I kid you not.
We are being surveyed,
by an alien species,
I call the Viewers.
And though they have yet
to emerge from their ship,
I believe they trust me.
If they didn't,
I don't think any of us
would be here right now.
So as I said,
in just under an hour,
Star Lasso Experience,
is gonna change you.
But first,
my boys are gonna come out
and do a little number for us.
Would that be alright?
Hustle. Go, go, go.
Alright.
My little satellites.
Colton, Phoenix, Max.
Remember those names, folks.
Alright, here we go!
What is that?
Do you guys see that?
Stay in your seats.
This is new.
They are early.
They are giving us a real show today.
That they are.
Yeah.
They are giving us a real show today.
They are ready, we are ready.
Welcome to the Star Lasso Experience,
only at Jupiter's Claim.
Please remember,
to avoid using your cell phones
Come on.
Or any flash photography during the event.
Cell phones off, you all.
Come on!
Bear with us now.
Trained animals can be unpredictable.
Now sit back,
stay in your seats,
and enjoy the Star Lasso Experien...
Well, cowboys and cowgirls,
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
That's right.
Happy trails.
It's closing time.
You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
Come back again.
And until then, we wish you well.
Hasta la vista.
Adios.
Well, cowboys and cowgirls,
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
That's right. Happy trails.
It's closing time.
You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
Come back again.
And until then...
Lucky.
Lucky, come on, come on.
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
Lucky.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Yo.
It's done.
Alright, I will be over in the
morning to tear that shit off.
Or you guys can do it yourselves.
It's all the same.
No, no.
I like when you do it.
Of course you do.
Alright.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Pick up, pick up, pick up,
pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up.
Come on, come on.
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
Did you know that the very
first assembly of photographs
in sequential order
to make a motion picture
was a two second clip
of a Black man on a horse?
That man was a Bahamian jockey
known as Alistair E. Haywood,
and he was my great great grandfather.
Hey.
Em.
I was right.
It's not a ship.
What happened?
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪ So I can so... ♪
What the fuck?
Shit.
It ate them Em.
It ate them all.
It's alive Em.
It's an animal.
It's territorial...
and it thinks that this is its home.
Em!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yes.
Hey, hey. We are in trouble.
Ok?
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
What?
What the fuck?
Who the hell is that?
Em!
Fuck.
It's above us.
Oh shit!
Shit.
Oh, shit! What the fuck?
Somebody please?
Oh, please! Help us!
Oh, God.
Something very bad is happening.
Fuck!
Yeah, we are fucked.
Nope.
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪ So I can... ♪
♪ It cuts my security ♪
♪ Has she got ♪
♪ Control of me? ♪
♪ I turn to her and say... ♪
Em?
OJ is coming.
Let's go.
Got to get out this house.
I got to get out this house.
No stop.
Can't we just wait, right?
You can.
No, I am not gonna be here alone.
I have got to get out
this fucking house!
We are alive still
because we stayed here.
Go!
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
Go.
Yeah, she...
she gonna make it.
OJ.
She gonna make it.
Oh, hey horsie.
Hey don't
Don't look him in the eyes please.
VFX!
Focus here.
Come on.
Go.
Welcome to my tavern.
I don't know if you have heard,
but a terrible beast is about.
It's been harassing villagers,
ruining crops and eating their livestock.
Many a glory seeking hunter,
has attempted to defeat it,
and just as many have perished.
While you are here...
While you are here, please look around.
I am here in Agua Dulce, California,
and the whereabouts of those
40 guests and employees
of a local Western theme park
are still unknown.
The sheriff's office has had its hands full
trying to identify the unaccounted for.
Until they do, only one thing is certain.
There is something strange
happening out here in Agua Dulce.
Security cameras were off at the time.
Other than that, we have
no reason to suspect foul play.
We did have a considerable amount
of rain come through here,
so we don't want to rule out flash flooding
as possibly having played
a part. We are obviously...
You never go wrong,
with a fried fish sandwich.
Tartar got tang.
Stupid.
Tartar got tang?
Got really?
I don't think it eats you
if you don't look it in the eye.
Hey, hey!
RTR bro.
You know?
Like read the room.
Nobody want to talk about that.
Let's go!
Ok, ok, ok. Enough.
Alright, alright, alright, alright, alright.
Hey, you lucky!
Every animal got rules.
Alright?
We know what it wants,
and we know how it comes so...
Fuck.
We don't really know shit.
OJ, what's this about man?
What's this about?
You want me to...
You want me to say...
I am sorry?
I was wrong? It's dumb?
It was not dumb.
Own the moment.
Stop.
It was good. It was good.
Stop, stop this shit.
But the moment about to pass.
And we don't own shit.
Ok. Well, I assume...
you all are crashing at mine.
Right, because you can.
Because I am not going back
to the fucking
monster umbrella.
Got to feed them.
Let Lucky out.
There is shit to do.
Always.
Always some shit to do.
There is a wheelchair on your roof.
Hi.
That cloud,
ain't moved a goddamn inch.
So you are not completely full of shit.
Thank you.
Yeah. Thank you.
The concept of extraterrestrial animals
in the sky,
is not a new thing.
You know, people been trying
to get pictures of these things
since like the '50s.
You know it's an ancient...
How do we see it?
It's gonna get hungry again.
So you know...
just ring the dinner bell.
Now, we know what it doesn't like.
That little fake horse
and flags messed it up good.
Got stuck in its windpipe or something.
I bet it ain't gonna fuck
with flags like that in a minute.
Yeah.
We pissed him off.
We are not the reason
it settled down here.
That was Jupe.
He got caught up
trying to tame a predator.
You can't do that.
You got to enter an agreement
with one.
Yeah.
Ask Siegfried and Roy.
Ok.
Asking as...
someone who was in the house
when the shit went down...
How exactly do you,
enter an agreement with a fucking...
a UFO,
alien entity or whatever
the hell you want to call it?
Jean Jacket.
Call him Jean Jacket.
So, how about this?
How about we...
send old Jean Jacket some fresh horses,
in golden hour and see what happens?
Horse people.
Why not just set them free?
We are not doing that.
Ok.
Who is gonna go...
down there
and get the star...
out of his trailer?
Me.
I will get him out.
Where you want it?
You draw him out there.
I am here.
On this ridge.
Oh, shit.
Made her myself.
No electricity.
Didn't I tell you this motherfucker,
was gonna come up here
with a nonelectrical camera?
Let's go boy!
Yeah!
I have been up under it
a couple times now.
I get him.
It's an animal.
You don't turn your back on a bear.
You don't wear red around a bull.
It's like that.
You don't look at it,
unless you want its attention.
Good night, Mr. Storeman.
Fuck it.
I call top hat.
And we ain't got a lot of time.
One day.
Two days tops.
Because the word is getting out,
and when it does...
Sorry, dead people.
Park is closed.
You know people gonna come
and do what they always do.
Try and take it all for themselves.
Fine.
Thimble.
That's the one I wanted anyway.
Well let them come.
It ain't gonna matter.
Because what we about to do...
they can't erase that.
He is big,
he is bad,
and he has got a lot of spirit.
But anything with a spirit can get broke.
So you break it.
I will get the shot.
Hey, I know.
What we are doing is important.
Right?
Like...
what we document,
it's...
it's gonna do some good?
I mean,
besides the money...
and fucking fame,
like, we can save some lives.
Fuck, we can even save Earth.
Alright?
Yeah.
♪ Well, it came down to Earth ♪
♪ And it hid in a tree ♪
♪ I said, Mr. Purple People Eater ♪
♪ Don't eat me ♪
♪ Well, he looked at me ♪
♪ and in a voice so gruff ♪
♪ He said I would not eat you ♪
♪ Because you are too tough ♪
♪ He was a oneeyed ♪
♪ onehorned ♪
♪ Flying purple people eater ♪
♪ Oneeyed, onehorned ♪
♪ Oneeyed ♪
♪ onehorned ♪
♪ Flying purple people eater ♪
♪ Sure looks strange to me ♪
He ain't gonna fuck with you.
Time to wake up the family.
Here we go.
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
♪ I came down on a lightning bolt ♪
♪ Nine months in my mama's belly ♪
♪ When I was born ♪
♪ the midwife screamed and shout ♪
♪ I had fire and brimstone ♪
♪ coming out of my mouth ♪
♪ I am Exuma ♪
How exquisitely stupid is that?
♪ Nanana Nana ♪
♪ Exuma was my name ♪
♪ when I lived in the stars ♪
♪ Exuma was a planet
♪ that once lit Mars ♪
♪ I have got the voices of many ♪
♪ in my throat ♪
♪ The teeth of a frog ♪
♪ and the tail of a goat ♪
♪ I am Exuma ♪
♪ I am the Obeah man ♪
♪ Nananana nanana ♪
♪ Nanana nanana ♪
We gonna get you today motherfucker.
♪ When I have got my ♪
♪ big hat on my head ♪
♪ You know that ♪
♪ I can raise the dead ♪
♪ And when I have got my stick in my hand ♪
♪ You know that I am... ♪
Where is the feed for Holst's camera?
Over.
Could not figure it out. Over.
What you mean,
you could not figure it out?
Over.
Holst is shooting on a film camera,
and all of our cameras are digital,
so it's a whole thing.
Over.
Basically, you forgot about it. Over.
Yeah well, I had my hands full
rigging 50 fucking sky dancers
to dead people's car batteries
all connected to one control panel.
So, yeah, fucking over.
Sorry.
I am scared.
Man down.
Man down? What?
Where?
Last dancer,
deep in the gulch.
Stay on it Em.
I am staying up.
Motherfucker.
Oh wait.
Oh, it's back up.
Could be a faulty battery.
Alright.
Shot is up then.
No, he is poking.
Who is this asshole?
Man in black on a white motorcycle.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Shit.
Can I help you?
You see that cloud?
Hey man, who you with?
Oh, I am sorry.
Who are you?
Nobody.
You don't look like a nobody to me.
Yeah look, we doing a camera test
for a Verizon commercial so...
now I am need you to clear the road.
This whole valley comes up as blurry
on Google Maps.
You are really tucked away back here.
Jupiter's Claim?
Quicker if you go the other way around.
Yeah.
Actually,
what did happen with Jupe Park
and all those people?
He was basically your neighbor right?
So what they vanished?
You don't believe the flood narrative, do you?
Fuck guys.
It's TMZ.
Oh, fuck me.
Hey guys.
Jean Jacket,
is definitely in those clouds,
and he is definitely coming this way.
What's the matter?
Don't you want to be on TV?
Man I am trying to tell you.
You don't want to go that way.
Fuck it.
Your loss, nobody.
We still rolling? Over.
Goddamn right we are.
Fellas, here it comes.
Over.
Pop quiz, guys.
What happens when an electric bike
going 60 miles per hour,
hits an anti electric field
going in the opposite direction?
Shit.
Fuck.
We are all gonna go to jail.
Oh, fuck. There is no way
that that guy is alive.
Shit.
Goddamn.
I told his ass not to go.
I told him not to go.
Hey OJ, what's...
Where the fuck are you going?
The fuck is he doing?
I am going dark. Over.
Ok. No, OJ no.
No. No. No self respecting...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Easy, easy, easy.
Did you get that on camera?
Look at me. Look at me.
Look at me.
What happened?
Listen, listen,
we got to get you out of here.
Eyes on me.
Where is my camera?
Hey!
I need my camera. Do you see it?
Ok.
Angel?
What?
Angel, come on.
We got to reload.
Shit.
Wait.
Where is your phone?
Why are not you filming this?
What?
Angel?
What's happening?
Ok.
OJ,
if you die trying to save
that guy, I will kill you.
No.
No, no, please.
Please, no. No.
We are gonna get you out.
Not before you take a picture.
Shut your eye.
Take a picture first!
Camera reloads.
You can use my camera.
There is not enough time.
It's here.
Be Scorpion King.
Make a name for yourself.
What is that?
My bad man.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
My camera! I need my camera!
Oh, my God! Fuck!
Give me the lid.
Come on. Alright.
Oh, God!
Oh, fuck!
Shit! Fuck!
Hey, hey! Is everybody ok?
For the love of fuck, talk to me please!
OJ.
OJ. OJ!
You stupid ass motherfucker,
you better answer me.
Are you ok?
Are you good?
Over.
Oh, God!
Oh, God.
Holy shit, I-I I think
it's taking the dancers.
Are you getting this?
Guys,
OJ is hooded up.
He is doing the run.
OJ is doing the run!
Oh, God.
Hey it's gone.
I can't see it anymore, guys.
Get it. Get it!
No.
Fuck.
Go! Go!
Lucky, go. Go, go, go, go, go!
Holy shit!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Yeah, he didn't like that, did he?
OJ,
you are a motherfucking genius.
We got it.
It's over.
It's over. We got it, you all!
The feed started going in and out when...
when that guy got got.
But we should be covered
with the film camera.
Right Holst?
The light.
The light it's...
gonna be magic soon.
What you mean Ant?
No, no. Wh-Where you going?
It's gonna be alright Angel.
We don't deserve the impossible.
Hey guys.
Holst just said some creepy, cryptic shit.
Took his camera.
He is heading up the mountain.
Over.
Hey Holst.
Holst. Wait. Hold on man.
Talk to me. What happened?
Did you get the shot or didn't you? Over.
This nigga.
Fuck it.
This is crazy right?
Come on, come on, come on.
Fuck.
No, man.
The fuck?
Holst.
Oh, shit.
Fuck!
Oh, God.
No.
Oh, shit.
Fuck. Fuck.
What?
Fuck.
Ok.
Fuck!
Em! Oh, shit!
Oh, no!
Help!
Hey!
Don't look. Don't look.
Don't look.
Get the bike!
Get out of here!
Oh, my God.
You are dead!
Dead!
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Look down.
Hey.
Come on.
No.
Oh, fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
No!
Just leave OJ.
Forget it! Come on!
Come on!
It's gonna fuck you up.
Come on.
Come on, come on!
What the...
Come on!
I am gonna get you, you motherfucker.
I am take you to Oprah.
Let's go to Oprah.
Yes!
Nobody fucks with Haywood, bitch!
Nobody!
You hear me!
Cowboys and cowgirls,
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
That's right.
Happy trails.
It's closing time.
You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
Come back again.
Until then,
we wish you well.
Hasta la vista.
Adios.
Yeah, get a shot of her.
Zoom in.
We are ready.
We are set up, ready to go.
Folks, this is Wally Pachenko
reporting live from Agua Dulce
just outside of Jupiter's Claim,
where just seconds ago
an inexplicable occurrence,
just in the distance...
You can probably hear,
the shock in my voice.
There are still some fragments,
floating in the air
where some some unidentified object
just drifted off into space and exploded.
You can see some fragments
still falling from the sky.
We will have some amazing...
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync October 2022